<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Momentu Android</string>

    <!-- Strings for login -->
    <string name="login_title">Momentu</string>
    <string name="prompt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_log_in">Login</string>
    <string name="username_not_exist">This user does not exist</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="confirm_registry">User name not found. You want to create a new account?</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <!-- Strings for search page-->
    <string name="action_voice_rec">action voice rec</string>
    <string name="action_location">action location</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="title_location_permission">Oops! Where are you?</string>
    <string name="text_location_permission">Momentu will ask for your permission to access your location.</string>
    <string name="ask_log_out">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>

    <!-- Example strings for example state and city-->
    <string-array name="States">
        <item>Please select state…</item>
        <item>Illinois</item>
        <item>California</item>
        <item>Ohio</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Cities">
        <item>Please select city…</item>
        <item>Chicago</item>
        <item>Aurora</item>
        <item>Joliet</item>
        <item>Rockford</item>>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example strings for feed activity -->
    <plurals name="likes_count">
        <item quantity="one">%d like</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d likes</item>
    </plurals>

    <string name="feed_hashtag">#Hawaii</string>
    <string name="feed_description_2">So we made it to Hawaii all safe and stuff</string>
    <string name="feed_description_1">Kauai, Hawaii | Dramatic Cliffs, Tropical Rainforests and Pristine Beaches.</string>



    <!-- Strings for term and policy -->
    <string name="term_and_policy_text">
        <![CDATA[

       <h2>Welcome!</h2>
       <p>We’ve drafted these Terms of Service (which we call the “Terms”) so you’ll know the rules
       that govern our relationship with you. Although we have tried our best to strip the legalese
       from the Terms, there are places where these Terms may still read like a traditional
       contract. There’s a good reason for that: These Terms do indeed form a legally binding
       contract between you and Momentu Inc. So please read them carefully.</p>
       <p>By using Momentu or any of our other products or services that link to these Terms
       (we refer to these simply as the “Services”), you agree to the Terms. Of course, if you
       don’t agree with them, then don’t use the Services.</p>
       <p>ARBITRATION NOTICE: THESE TERMS CONTAIN AN ARBITRATION CLAUSE</a> A LITTLE LATER ON.
       EXCEPT FOR CERTAIN TYPES OF DISPUTES MENTIONED IN THAT ARBITRATION CLAUSE, YOU AND MOMENTU
       INC. AGREE THAT DISPUTES BETWEEN US WILL BE RESOLVED BY MANDATORY BINDING ARBITRATION,
       AND YOU AND MOMENTU INC. WAIVE ANY RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS-ACTION LAWSUIT OR
       CLASS-WIDE ARBITRATION.</p>

       <h2>1. Who Can Use the Services</h2>
       <p>No one under 13 is allowed to create an account or use the Services. We may offer
       additional Services with additional terms that may require you to be even older to use
       them. So please read all terms carefully.</p>
       <p>By using the Services, you state that:</p>
       <ul>
            <li>You can form a binding contract with Momentu Inc.</li>
            <li>You are not a person who is barred from receiving the Services under the laws of
            the United States or any other applicable jurisdiction—meaning that you do not appear
            on the U.S. Treasury Department’s list of Specially Designated Nationals or face any
            other similar prohibition.</li>
            <li>  You will comply with these Terms and all applicable local, state, national, and
            international laws, rules, and regulations.</li>
       </ul>
       <p>If you are using the Services on behalf of a business or some other entity, you state
       that you are authorized to grant all licenses set forth in these Terms and to agree to these
       Terms on behalf of the business or entity. If you are using the Services on behalf of an
       entity of the U.S. Government, you agree to the Amendment to Momentu Inc. Terms of Service
       for U.S. Government Users.</p>

       <h2>Contact us</h2>
       <p>We welcome comments, questions, concerns, or suggestions.</p>

        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
